Sepopo
o i vardei
EMPH V look
look
sunya li a nim i do i dami
zero time SUBJ I V can V exist
I can never be
no yuloa fano
as perfect child
the perfect daughter
ilie
likelihood
maybe
daehun i elori no
if-consequence V act as
if I act as
elireva
true
elihei eta i tinen
self then V break
self then I will break
e visfiyur de fa
OBJ heart of family
my family's heart
cei noi faejor
question-who here woman
who is this woman
ca i ciuta-vardei e nim?
CONN V direct-look OBJ I?
that is looking straight at me?
ceora a nim e sepopo i ilivargorum?
why SUBJ I OBJ reflection V recognize-not?
why don't I recognize my reflection?
noder i aniliear
even V try-COMPL
though I tried
mai i doum i hehou
but V can-not V hide
I cannot hide
celi popo i ciudonis
when reflection V show-PROSP
when will my reflection show
e elireva nim?
OBJ true I?
the true me?
celi popo i ciudonis
when reflection V show-PROSP
when will my reflection show
e elireva nim?
OBJ true I?
the true me?